4wheelonline.com 2018-05-10

# Privacy Policy | 4WheelOnline.com

## Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy

* * *

4WheelOnline.com respects your privacy. Across our business, around the world, we will only collect, store and use your personal information for defined purposes. We use your information to support and enhance our relationship with you, for example, to process your purchase, provide service and support, and share product, service and company news and offerings with you. We do not sell your personal information. We only share your personal data outside the 4WheelOnline.com family of companies with your consent, as required by law or to protect 4WheelOnline.com, its customers, or the public, or with companies that help 4WheelOnline.com fulfill its obligations with you, and then only with partners who share 4WheelOnline.com's commitment to protecting your privacy and data. At any time you may contact 4WheelOnline.com with any privacy questions or concerns you may have. You also may ask at any time to see the personal data you have given us and request correction or deletion. We strive to protect the security of your personal data by use of appropriate measures and processes. 

* * *

### 4WheelOnline.com only uses your personal information for specific purposes

The information you provide will be kept confidential and used to support your customer relationship with 4WheelOnline.com. Among other things, we want to help you quickly find information on 4WheelOnline.com and alert you to product updates, special offers, updated information and other new products and services from 4WheelOnline.com. Agents or contractors of 4WheelOnline.com who have access to your personal information and prospect information are required to keep the information confidential and not use it for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for 4WheelOnline.com. 4WheelOnline.com may enhance or merge your information collected at its site with data from third parties for purposes of marketing products or services to you. 

In addition, 4WheelOnline.com may be required to disclose personal information in connection with law enforcement, fraud prevention, regulation, and other legal action or if 4WheelOnline.com reasonably believes it is necessary to do so to protect 4WheelOnline.com, its customers, or the public. 

* * *

### 4WheelOnline.com will not disclose your personal information to any outside organization for its use in marketing without your consent

Information regarding you (such as name, address and phone number) or your order and the products you purchase will not be given or sold to any outside organization for its use in marketing or solicitation without your consent. Your information may be shared with agents or contractors of 4WheelOnline.com for the purpose of performing services for 4WheelOnline.com.

* * *
